UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs
1998-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 10
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/050 P
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Photographs.
7101244
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of over three hundred photographs. Most of the photographs were taken between 1997 and 2000.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications
Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile workers -- Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 10 (New York, N.Y.)--Photographs; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.)--Photographs; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)--Photographs; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union -- Photographs
7101244
- 1997-2000 Plus some old photographs (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  124 photographs
- 1997-2000 plus some old photographs (Box 1, Folder 2)
  160 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 3)
  24 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  3 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 5)
  17 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 6)
  6 photographs
- Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hillary Clinton Photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
  1
- Global Justice for Workers (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Global Justice for Workers (folder 2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1998 Photograph negatives and Contact Sheets (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1999 Photograph negatives and Contact Sheets (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 155 Photographs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  4 photographs
- Photograph of Asian workers (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Photograph of Asian workers (Box 1, Folder 15)
  1 photograph
- Contact sheets and negatives (Box 1, Folder 16)